Finding Aid for Washtenaw County (Mich.)Publications, 1952-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Washtenaw County (Mich.) publications 1952-1981
Washtenaw County (Mich.)
1 linear ft.
94163 Cb 2
Miscellaneous publications of various Washtenaw County government offices and departments.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The Washtenaw County (Mich.) Publications were received as individual items or as part of various accessions.
The publications are open without restriction.
Miscellaneous publications of various Washtenaw County government offices and departments
Subjects:
Washtenaw County (Mich.)--Politics and government.
Contributors:
Washtenaw County (Mich.). Board of Supervisors.; Washtenaw County Community Services Agency.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). County Clerk.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). County Treasurer.; Washtenaw County Defense Council.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). Dept. of Weights and Measures.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). Division of Building Inspection.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). Drain Commissioner.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). Friend of the Court.; Washtenaw County Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice Committee.; Washtenaw County Medical Examiner.; Washtenaw County Parks and Recreation Commission.; Michigan. Probate Court (Washtenaw County). Juvenile Division.; Washtenaw County (Mich.). Prosecuting Attorney.; Washtenaw County Road Commission.
- Department Publications
  - Budget
    - 1959-1969 (11 vols.) (Box 1)
  - Board of Supervisors
    - Actions of the Washtenaw County Board of Supervisors relating to the Portage Lake level problem, [1958] (Box 1)
    - Proposed annual budget for the year 1958 (Box 1)
  - Community Services Agency
    - Annual report, 1968 (Box 1)
  - County Clerk
    - Annual report, 1961 (Box 1)
  - County Treasurer
    - Annual report, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Defense Council
    - Washtenaw County civil defense plan, [1953 ?] (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Public Works
    - Washtenaw County solid waste management plan, May 1990 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Weights and Measures
    - Annual report, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Division of Building Inspection
    - Annual report, 1955 1959 (Box 1)
  - Drain Commission
    - Annual report, 1957/58 1966 1968, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Controlling urban stormwater runoff in Washtenaw County, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Rules [for subdivision drainage], 1979 (Box 1)
  - Friend of the Court
    - Annual report, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice Committee
    - A comprehensive program for law enforcement and criminal justice planning in Washtenaw County, 1969. (Box 1)
  - Medical Examiner
    - Annual report, 1962/66 (Box 1)
  - Parks and Recreation Commission
    - Annual report, 1975 1978 (Box 1)
    - Recreation behaviors and attitudes of residents of Washtenaw County, by Jerome Johnston, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Probate and Juvenile Court
    - Annual report, 1952-1955, (4 vols.) (Box 1)
    - Committee reports of Project 74, 1967 (Box 1)
    - A study of the Juvenile Division of the Washtenaw Probate Court, 1965
      - Part 1: Court and probation services, by Jay D. Olson (Box 1)
      - Part 2: Detention services, by Gordon D. Nelson (Box 1)
      - Part 3: Police services, by Jesse R. James (Box 1)
  - Prosecuting Attorney
    - Annual report, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Road Commission
    - Standards and specifications for plat development and street construction, 1968 (Box 1)